<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>A Girl Has No R Blog</title>
    <link>/</link>
    <description>Recent content on A Girl Has No R Blog</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Sun, 12 May 2019 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>An Introvert&#39;s Guide to Conferences</title>
      <link>/2019/05/an-introvert-s-guide-to-conferences/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 12 May 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/2019/05/an-introvert-s-guide-to-conferences/</guid>
      <description>It’s a rainy Sunday here in NYC, and I have some time to reflect on the Lander Analytics RStatsNY conference I attended for the last few days. It was a whirlwind - tons of learning, laughs, shock and awe (redoc I’m looking at you), and of course a steady sprinkle of imposter syndrome and anxiety. I had an absolute blast, the survival analysis workshop was phenomenal and I’m already planning to trick my boss into sending me next year.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Lock all the legs!</title>
      <link>/2019/04/lock-all-the-legs/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 30 Apr 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/2019/04/lock-all-the-legs/</guid>
      <description>Welcome, friends, to my first data post! So here’s the background: I love brazilian jiu jitsu (bjj). I did martial arts when I was a kid (bonus story at the end about my favorite martial art moment ever), but stopped going after I had a knee injury that sidelined me for several months. I’d always toyed with the idea of going back, but my wife made me realize how much I actually missed sports when I saw her being crazy active with her HIIT gym.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Finally! A Blog!</title>
      <link>/2019/04/hello-world/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 26 Apr 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/2019/04/hello-world/</guid>
      <description>Well this took me way too long to get up and running! But here we are :) Hello, and welcome! Why another R blog?I’m starting this blog for a few reasons. First, I want to use it as a way to document my own R journey. I figured I’d document it for lots of reasons: a way to showcase my own work, career development, networking, everyone in the R community says you should do it, blah blah blah.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>